♪ I can't fool myself ♪
♪ I don't want nobody else ♪
♪ To ever love me ♪
♪ You are my shinin' star ♪
♪ My guiding light, my love fantasy ♪
♪ There's not a minute, hour, day ♪
♪ Or night that I don't love you ♪
♪ You're at the top of my list ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm always thinkin' of you ♪
♪ I still remember in the days ♪
♪ When I was scared to touch you ♪
♪ How I spent my day dreamin' plannin' ♪
♪ How to say I love you ♪
♪ You must have known that ♪
♪ I had feelings deep enough to swim in ♪
♪ That's when you opened up your heart ♪
♪ And you told me to come in ♪
♪ Oh, my love ♪
♪ A thousand kisses from you ♪
♪ Is never too much ♪
♪ I just don't wanna stop ♪
♪ Oh, my love ♪
♪ A million days in your arms ♪
♪ Is never too much ♪
♪ I just don't wanna stop ♪
♪ Too much, never too much ♪
♪ Never too much, never too much ♪
♪ Woke up today, looked at your picture ♪
♪ Just to get me started ♪
♪ I called you up ♪
♪ But you weren't there ♪
♪ And I was broken hearted ♪
♪ Hung up the phone, can't be too late ♪
♪ The boss is so demandin' ♪
♪ Opened the door up and to my surprise ♪
♪ There you were standin' ♪
♪ Well, who needs to go to work ♪
♪ To hustle for another dollar ♪
♪ I'd rather be with you ♪
♪ 'Cause you make my heart ♪
♪ Scream and holler ♪
♪ Love is a gamble ♪
♪ And I'm so glad that I'm winnin' ♪
♪ We've come a long way ♪
♪ And yet this is only the beginnin' ♪
♪ Oh, my love ♪
♪ A thousand kisses from you ♪
♪ Is never too much ♪
♪ Never too much, never too much ♪
♪ Never too much ♪
♪ I just don't wanna stop ♪
♪ Oh, my love ♪
♪ A million days in your arms ♪
♪ Is never too much ♪
♪ Never too much, never too much ♪
♪ Never too much ♪
♪ And I just don't wanna stop ♪
♪ Oh, my love ♪
♪ A thousand kisses from you is never ♪
♪ Never too much, never too much ♪
♪ Never, never, never ♪
♪ I just don't wanna stop ♪